[
  {
    "id": "1",
    "Question": "When Honeywell Founded",
    "answer": ["1905", "1990", "1885", "2000"],
    "type": "obj"
  },
  {
    "id": "2",
    "Question": "What is the boiling temperature of petrol?",
    "answer": ["40-120 째C", "120-180 째C", "180-250 째C", "250-320 째C"],
    "type": "obj"
  },
  {
    "id": "3",
    "Question": "Unit of Density ",
    "answer": ["Kg/m3", "Kg/m2"],
    "type": "obj"
  },
  {
    "id": "4",
    "Question": "MSC-L stands for",
    "answer": [
      "Multistream Controller for Loading",
      "Multiple Controller Leveler",
      "Multiple Communication for Local Data",
      "Multimedia Controller for Loading"
    ],
    "type": "obj"
  },
  {
    "id": "5",
    "Question": "ANPR stands for",
    "answer": [
      "Automatic Number plate recognition",
      "Automatic New Person recognition",
      "Automatic Number of People recognition",
      "Automatic Name Phone Retriever"
    ],
    "type": "obj"
  },
  {
    "id": "7",
    "Question": "ChatGPT stands for",
    "answer": [
      "Chat Generative Pre-Trained Transformer",
      "Chat That Generates Proper Text",
      "Chat generation for Public Tutor",
      "Chat Generated for Public Transmitted Request"
    ],
    "type": "obj"
  },
  {
    "id": "8",
    "Question": "TFMS stands for",
    "answer": [
      "Tank Farm Management System",
      "Tractor & Farm Management System",
      "Total Finance Management System",
      "Technical Firmware Management System"
    ],
    "type": "obj"
  },
  {
    "id": "9",
    "Question": "OCR stands for",
    "answer": [
      "Optical Character Recognition",
      "Original Car Recognition",
      "Obstructive Cable Recognition",
      "Original Channel Retrieval"
    ],
    "type": "obj"
  },
  {
    "id": "10",
    "Question": "API stands for",
    "answer": ["Application programming interface"],
    "type": "obj"
  },
  {
    "id": "11",
    "Question": "Which is not a browser",
    "answer": ["Bravo", "Thar", "Safari", "Tor"],
    "type": "obj"
  },
  {
    "id": "12",
    "Question": "What is RFID",
    "answer": ["Radio Frequency Identification tag"],
    "type": "obj"
  },
  {
    "id": "13",
    "Question": "Which is not a mobile OS",
    "answer": [
      "Android (Google)",
      "iOS (Apple)",
      "Bada (Samsung)",
      "Sailfish",
      "All of the above"
    ],
    "type": "obj"
  },
  {
    "id": "14",
    "Question": "It occurs once in a minute, twice in a moment, but never in an hour",
    "answer": ["M"],
    "type": "obj"
  }
]
